J. Peter Lesley Papers 1826-1898 Mss.B.L56
American Philosophical Society
- Series I. General correspondence, 1826-1898 (Box 1)
  - to Peter Lesley, Sr., 1840 August 21; Lesley, J. P., (J. Peter), 1819-1903 (Box 2)
  - to Mrs. S. E. Lesley., 1840 August 29; Lesley, J. P., (J. Peter), 1819-1903 (Box 2)
  - to [Mrs. Sarah Allen]., 1840 August 31; Lesley, J. P., (J. Peter), 1819-1903 (Box 2)
  - to J. Peter Lesley, with copy of birth certificate., 1840 September 8; Lesley, Peter (Box 2)
  - to Aunt Hall, 1840 September 26; Lesley, J. P., (J. Peter), 1819-1903 (Box 2)
  - to Peter Lesley, Sr., 1840 September 30; Lesley, J. P., (J. Peter), 1819-1903 (Box 2)
  - to Mrs. S. E. Lesley, 1840 October 9; Lesley, J. P., (J. Peter), 1819-1903 (Box 2)
  - to [Peter Lesley, Sr.?], n.d.[ca. 1840]; Lesley, J. P., (J. Peter), 1819-1903 (Box 2)
  - to Miss E[lizabeth] Lesley., 1841 February 20; Lesley, J. P., (J. Peter), 1819-1903 (Box 2)
  - to [Peter Lesley], 1841 April 12; Alexander, J. A. (Box 2)
  - to J. Peter Lesley, 1841 April 14; Petrikin, H. (Box 2)
  - to [Peter Lesley, Sr.], 1841 May(?) 14; Lesley, J. P., (J. Peter), 1819-1903 (Box 2)
  - to Susan I. Lyman, 1841 May 26; Hale, Sarah E. (Box 2)
  - to Peter Lesley, Sr., 1841 June 10; Lesley, J. P., (J. Peter), 1819-1903 (Box 2)
  - to [Peter Lesley, Sr.], 1841 June 11; Lesley, J. P., (J. Peter), 1819-1903 (Box 2)
  - to Mrs. Anna Wilson, 1841 July 16; Lesley, J. P., (J. Peter), 1819-1903 (Box 2)
  - to Peter Lesley, Sr., 1841 July 24; Lesley, J. P., (J. Peter), 1819-1903 (Box 2)
  - to Mrs. S. E. Lesley, 1841 September 3; Lesley, J. P., (J. Peter), 1819-1903 (Box 2)
  - to Peter Lesley, Sr., 1841 September 5; Lesley, J. P., (J. Peter), 1819-1903 (Box 2)
  - to Peter Lesley, Sr., 1841 September 27; Lesley, J. P., (J. Peter), 1819-1903 (Box 2)
  - to E[lizabeth] Lesley, 1841 October 7; Lesley, J. P., (J. Peter), 1819-1903 (Box 2)
  - to [Peter Lesley, Sr.], 1841 October 19; Lesley, J. P., (J. Peter), 1819-1903 (Box 2)
  - to Peter Lesley, 1841 November 1; Bache, A.D., (Alexander Dallas), 1806-1867 (Box 2)
  - to Peter Lesley, Sr., 1841 December 7; Lesley, J. P., (J. Peter), 1819-1903 (Box 2)
  - to Peter Lesley, Sr., 1842 February 14; Lesley, J. P., (J. Peter), 1819-1903 (Box 2)
  - to [Peter Lesley]., 1842 March 28; Lesley, J. P., (J. Peter), 1819-1903 (Box 2)
  - to [Peter Lesley, Sr.], 1842 April 4; Lesley, J. P., (J. Peter), 1819-1903 (Box 2)
  - to [Peter Lesley, Sr.], 1842 April 11; Lesley, J. P., (J. Peter), 1819-1903 (Box 2)
  - to Peter Lesley, Sr., 1842 June 7; Lesley, J. P., (J. Peter), 1819-1903 (Box 2)
  - to Mrs. S. E. Lesley, 1842 July 15; Lesley, J. P., (J. Peter), 1819-1903 (Box 2)
  - to J. Peter Lesley., 1842 August 19; Davis, William A. (Box 2)
  - to Peter Lesley, Sr., 1842 September 7; Lesley, J. P., (J. Peter), 1819-1903 (Box 2)
  - to [Susan I. Lyman Lesley and Catherine Lyman]., 1842 October 27; Child, Lydia Maria, 1802-1880 (Box 2)
  - [Peter Lesley, Sr.], [1842 November 26]; Lesley, J. P., (J. Peter), 1819-1903 (Box 2)
  - to [Peter Lesley, Sr.], 1843 January 19; Lesley, J. P., (J. Peter), 1819-1903 (Box 2)
  - to Peter Lesley, Sr., 1843 February 8; Lesley, J. P., (J. Peter), 1819-1903 (Box 2)
  - to [Mrs. S. E. Lesley]., 1843 February 17; Lesley, J. P., (J. Peter), 1819-1903 (Box 2)
  - to [Mrs. Anna Wilson] and [Aunt Hall]., 1843 March 2; Lesley, J. P., (J. Peter), 1819-1903 (Box 2)
  - to Peter Lesley, Sr., 1843 March 6; Lesley, J. P., (J. Peter), 1819-1903 (Box 2)
  - to Peter Lesley, Sr., 1843 March 13; Lesley, J. P., (J. Peter), 1819-1903 (Box 2)
  - to [Peter Lesley, Sr.], 1843 April 7; Lesley, J. P., (J. Peter), 1819-1903 (Box 2)
  - to Susan I. Lyman, 1843 May 5; Hale, Sarah E. (Box 2)
  - to [Peter Lesley, Sr.], 1843 August 24; Lesley, J. P., (J. Peter), 1819-1903 (Box 2)
  - to [Peter Lesley, Sr.], 1843 August 24; Lesley, J. P., (J. Peter), 1819-1903 (Box 2)
  - to [Peter Lesley, Sr.], 1843 September 15; Lesley, J. P., (J. Peter), 1819-1903 (Box 2)
  - to Peter Lesley, Sr., 1843 November 8; Lesley, J. P., (J. Peter), 1819-1903 (Box 2)
  - to Mrs. S. E. Lesley, 1843 December 1; Lesley, J. P., (J. Peter), 1819-1903 (Box 2)
  - to Mrs. S. E. Lesley, 1844 January 9; Lesley, J. P., (J. Peter), 1819-1903 (Box 2)
  - to [Peter Lesley, Sr.], 1844 February 5; Lesley, J. P., (J. Peter), 1819-1903 (Box 2)
  - to Mrs. Anna Wilson, 1844 February 7; Lesley, J. P., (J. Peter), 1819-1903 (Box 2)
  - to [Peter Lesley, Sr.], 1844 February 9; Lesley, J. P., (J. Peter), 1819-1903 (Box 2)
  - to [Mrs.] Susan I[nches] Lyman [Lesley], [1844 February 23]; Davis, William A. (Box 2)
  - to [Mrs. S. E. Lesley, 1844 February 27; Lesley, J. P., (J. Peter), 1819-1903 (Box 2)
  - to Peter Lesley, Sr., 1844 March 11; Lesley, J. P., (J. Peter), 1819-1903 (Box 2)
  - to Peter Lesley, Sr., 1844 May 17; Lesley, J. P., (J. Peter), 1819-1903 (Box 2)
  - to Mrs. S. E. Lesley, 1844 May 30; Lesley, J. P., (J. Peter), 1819-1903 (Box 2)
  - to Mrs. E. L. Stilwell, 1844 June 3; Lesley, J. P., (J. Peter), 1819-1903 (Box 2)
  - to Peter Lesley, Sr., 1844 July 4; Lesley, J. P., (J. Peter), 1819-1903 (Box 2)
  - to Mr. A. Lesley, 1844 July 8; Lesley, J. P., (J. Peter), 1819-1903 (Box 2)
  - to [Peter Lesley]., 1844 July 20; Lesley, J. P., (J. Peter), 1819-1903 (Box 2)
  - to Peter Lesley., 1844 July 22; Lesley, J. P., (J. Peter), 1819-1903 (Box 2)
  - to Peter Lesley, 1844 August 1; Lesley, J. P., (J. Peter), 1819-1903 (Box 2)
  - to Peter Lesley, 1844 August 3; Lesley, J. P., (J. Peter), 1819-1903 (Box 2)
  - to Mrs. E.L. Stilwell, 1844 August 10; Lesley, J. P., (J. Peter), 1819-1903 (Box 2)
  - to Henry Lesley [and to Mrs. E.L. Stilwell], 1844 August 21; Lesley, J. P., (J. Peter), 1819-1903 (Box 2)
  - to Mrs. S. E. Lesley, 1844 August 2; Lesley, J. P., (J. Peter), 1819-1903 (Box 2)
  - to Allen Lesley, 1844 September 26; Lesley, J. P., (J. Peter), 1819-1903 (Box 2)
  - to Peter Lesley, 1844 September 12; Lesley, J. P., (J. Peter), 1819-1903 (Box 2)
  - to [Mrs.] Susan [Lesley]., 1844 September 24; Child, Lydia Maria, 1802-1880 (Box 2)
  - to Susan Lyman [Lesley]., 1844 September 30; Benzon, Edmund L. (Box 2)
  - to Mr. and Mrs. Elias Stilwell., 1844 October 5; Lesley, J. P., (J. Peter), 1819-1903 (Box 2)
  - to, 1844 October 5; Lesley, J. P., (J. Peter), 1819-1903 (Box 2)
  - to Mrs. S. E. Lesley, 1844 October 20; Lesley, J. P., (J. Peter), 1819-1903 (Box 2)
  - to Henry [Lesley], 1844 November 9; Lesley, J. P., (J. Peter), 1819-1903 (Box 2)
  - to Allen Lesley, 1844 Nov. 19; Lesley, J. P., (J. Peter), 1819-1903 (Box 2)
  - to Mrs. Elizabeth L. Stilwell, 1844 Nov. 20; Lesley, J. P., (J. Peter), 1819-1903 (Box 2)
  - to Mrs. Peter Lesley, 1844 Nov. 28; Lesley, J. P., (J. Peter), 1819-1903 (Box 2)
  - to Peter Lesley, 1844 Dec. 1; Schulte, A. (Box 2)
  - to W. Martin, editor of The Presbyterian, 1844 Dec. 29; Lesley, J. P., (J. Peter), 1819-1903 (Box 2)
  - Notes of foreign travel, in The Presbyterian., 1844-5; Lesley, J. P., (J. Peter), 1819-1903 (Box 2)
  - Receipts, tickets, etc. for travel in Europe..., 1844-1845; Lesley, J. P., (J. Peter), 1819-1903 (Box 2)
  - to Allen Lesley, 1845 Jan. 4; Lesley, J. P., (J. Peter), 1819-1903 (Box 2)
  - to Mrs. S. E. Lesley, 1845 Feb. 7; Lesley, J. P., (J. Peter), 1819-1903 (Box 2)
  - to Peter Lesley, 1845 Mar. 3; Lesley, J. P., (J. Peter), 1819-1903 (Box 2)
  - to J. Peter Lesley, 1845 Oct. 15; Wandel, Franz (Box 2)
  - to J. Peter Lesley, 1846 July 20; Bost, A. (Box 3)
  - to J. Peter Lesley, 1846 Oct. 10; Perston, Jessie (Box 3)
  - to Mrs. Susan Lesley, 1847 Jan. 1; Child, Lydia Maria, 1802-1880 (Box 3)
  - to Mrs. Maria Child, 1847 Mar. 25; Bremer, Frederika (Box 3)
  - to Mrs. Susan Lesley, 1847 Mar. 28; Child, Lydia Maria, 1802-1880 (Box 3)
  - and Marie Bost J. Peter Lesley, 1847 Apr. 8; Bost, A. (Box 3)
  - to Mrs. Susan Lesley, 1847? Apr.9; Child, Lydia Maria, 1802-1880 (Box 3)
  - to Susan Lyman Lesley, 1847 May 2; Child, Lydia Maria, 1802-1880 (Box 3)
  - to Mrs. Susan Lesley, 1847? May 4; Child, Lydia Maria, 1802-1880 (Box 3)
  - to Mrs. Susan Lesley, 1847 May 6; Hopper, Rosa (Box 3)
  - to Mrs. Susan Lesley, 1847 May 13; Hopper, John (Box 3)
  - to J. Peter Lesley, 1847 May 15, 16; Perston, Jessie (Box 3)
  - to Mrs. Susan Lesley, 1847 May 19; Hopper, Rosa (Box 3)
  - to J. Peter Lesley, 1847 June 15; Hall, James (Box 3)
  - to J. Peter Lesley, 1847 June 18; Hall, James (Box 3)
  - to Susan Lyman Lesley, 1847 July 4; Child, Lydia Maria, 1802-1880 (Box 3)
  - to J. Peter Lesley, 1847 July 31; Perston, Jessie (Box 3)
  - to Susan Lyman Lesley, 1847 Aug. 8; Child, Lydia Maria, 1802-1880 (Box 3)
  - to J. Peter Lesley, 1847 Aug. 23; Bost, A. (Box 3)
  - to J. Peter Lesley, 1847 Aug. 29; Perston, Jessie (Box 3)
  - to Mrs. Susan Lesley, 1847 Oct. 4; Hopper, Rosa (Box 3)
  - Philip Wandell to J. Peter Lesley, 1847 Oct. 4 (Box 3)
  - to Susan Lyman Lesley, 1847 Oct. 10; Child, Lydia Maria, 1802-1880 (Box 3)
  - to J. Peter Lesley, 1847 Oct. 29; Perston, Jessie (Box 3)
  - to Mrs. Susan Lesley, 1847? Nov. 4; Child, Lydia Maria, 1802-1880 (Box 3)
  - to J. Peter Lesley, 1847 Dec. 3; Bost, A. (Box 3)
  - to Susan Lyman Lesley, 1847?; Child, Lydia Maria, 1802-1880 (Box 3)
  - to Mrs. Susan Lesley, Child, Lydia Maria, 1802-1880 (Box 3)
  - to Mrs. Susan Lesley, 1847?-1848?; Child, Lydia Maria, 1802-1880 (Box 3)
  - to Susan Lesley, 1847; Child, Lydia Maria, 1802-1880 (Box 3)
  - to Mrs. Susan Lesley, 1847?; Child, Lydia Maria, 1802-1880 (Box 3)
  - to Mrs. Susan Lesley, Child, Lydia Maria, 1802-1880 (Box 3)
  - to Susan Lyman Lesley, 1847?; Child, Lydia Maria, 1802-1880 (Box 3)
  - to J. Peter Lesley, 1848 Jan. 7; Wandel, Franz (Box 3)
  - to Mrs. Susan Lesley, 1848 Jan. 12; Child, Lydia Maria, 1802-1880 (Box 3)
  - to Mrs. Susan Lesley, 1848 Jan. 14; Hopper, Rosa (Box 3)
  - to J. Peter Lesley, 1848 Feb. 1; Perston, Jessie (Box 3)
  - Charles Sedgwick to Mrs. Susan Lesley, 1848 1848 Mar. 11 (Box 3)
  - to Mrs. Susan Lesley, 1848 July 7; Hopper, Rosa (Box 3)
  - to Susan Lyman Lesley, 1848 Aug. 7; Child, Lydia Maria, 1802-1880 (Box 3)
  - to Mrs. Susan Lesley, 1848 Aug. 24; Hopper, Rosa (Box 3)
  - to J. Peter Lesley, 1848 Sept. 14; Bost, A. (Box 3)
  - Mrs. Elizabeth Gay to Peter Lesley, 1848 Oct. 19 (Box 3)
  - Mrs. Elizabeth Gay to Susan I. Lyman, 1848 Oct. 19 (Box 3)
  - to Mrs. Susan Lesley, 1848 Oct. 20; Hopper, John (Box 3)
  - to Mrs. Susan Inches Lyman Lesley, 1848 Oct. 22; Davis, William A. (Box 3)
  - Martha Cochrane to Susan Inches Lyman, 1848 Oct. (Box 3)
  - to Mrs. Susan Lesley, 1848 Dec. 24; Hopper, John (Box 3)
  - Study on increase in U.S. population, 1848?; Lesley, J. P., (J. Peter), 1819-1903 (Box 3)
  - to Susan Lyman Lesley, 1849 Jan. 4; Hopper, Rosa (Box 3)
  - to J. Peter Lesley, 1849 Jan. 6; Bost, A. (Box 3)
  - to Mrs. Susan Lesley, 1849 Jan. 28; Child, Lydia Maria, 1802-1880 (Box 3)
  - E. B. Inches to Mrs. Susan Lesley, 1849 Feb. 2 (Box 3)
  - to Mrs. Susan Lesley, 1849 Mar. 29; Hopper, Rosa (Box 3)
  - Concerning the intellect and the heart, 1849 Apr. 8; Lesley, J. P., (J. Peter), 1819-1903 (Box 3)
  - to J. Peter Lesley, 1849 Apr. 29; Hall, James (Box 3)
  - to Mrs. Susan Lesley, 1850 Jan. 16; Howe, S. L. (Box 3)
  - to J. Peter Lesley, 1850 Feb. 20; Wandel, Franz (Box 3)
  - to Mrs. Susan Lesley, 1850 Mar. 28; Hopper, Rosa (Box 3)
  - to J. Peter Lesley, 1850 Apr. 4; Bost, Marie (Box 3)
  - to Mrs. Susan Lesley, 1850 Apr. 4; Bost, Marie (Box 3)
  - to J. Peter Lesley, 1850 May 3; Trumbull, David (Box 3)
  - to J. Peter Lesley, 1850 May 7; Robie, Edward (Box 3)
  - to J. Peter Lesley, 1850 May 20; Trumbull, David (Box 3)
  - to Peter Lesley, 1850 May 29; Whelpley, J. D. (Box 3)
  - to J. Peter Lesley?, 1850 July 18; Trumbull, David (Box 3)
  - to Mrs. Peter Lesley, 1850 July 19; Francis, Convers (Box 3)
  - to Mrs. Susan Lesley, 1850 July 31; Russell, Ida (Box 3)
  - to J. Peter Lesley, 1850 Aug. 1; Rogers, Henry D., (Henry Darwin), 1806-1866 (Box 3)
  - to J. Peter Lesley, 1850 Aug. 2; Johnson, Samuel (Box 3)
  - to J. Peter Lesley, 1850 Aug. 20; Trumbull, David (Box 3)
  - to J. P. Lesley, 1850 Aug. 23; Mann, Horace, 1796-1859 (Box 3)
  - to J. Peter Lesley, 1850 Aug.; Rogers, Henry D., (Henry Darwin), 1806-1866 (Box 3)
  - to Peter Lesley, 1850 Sept. 2; Bushnell, George (Box 3)
  - to J. Peter Lesley, 1850 Sept. 12; Robie, Edward (Box 3)
  - o Susie I. Lesley, 1850? Sept. 14; Head, Mary (Box 3)
  - to J. Peter Lesley, 1850 Sept. 16; Bushnell, Horace, 1802-1876 (Box 3)
  - to J. P. Lesley, 1850 Sept. 16; Mann, Horace, 1796-1859 (Box 3)
  - to Mrs. Susan Lesley, 1850 Sept.; Child, Lydia Maria, 1802-1880 (Box 3)
  - to Mrs. Susan Lesley, 1850 Sept.; Ware, Lizzie (Box 3)
  - to Mrs. Susan Lesley, 1850 Oct. 13; Child, Lydia Maria, 1802-1880 (Box 3)
  - to J. Peter Lesley, 1850 Oct. 22; Seeley, R. H. (Box 3)
  - Hannah C. Stearns to Mrs. Susan Leslie [sic], 1850 Oct. 23 (Box 3)
  - to J. P. Lesley, 1850 Nov. 6; Quincy, Edmund (Box 3)
  - James Munroe to J. Peter Lesley, 1850 Nov. 8 (Box 3)
  - Ida Russell to Mrs. Susan Lesley, 1850 Nov. 13 (Box 3)
  - Warren Loring to J. Peter Lesley, 1850 Nov. 14 (Box 3)
  - Mrs. Mary H. Head to Susie Mrs. Susan I. Lesley, 1850 Nov. 17 (Box 3)
  - to J. P. Lesley, 1850 Nov. 22; Seeley, R. H. (Box 3)
  - to J. Peter Lesley, 1850 Nov. 26; Loring, Warren (Box 3)
  - to J. Peter Lesley, 1850 Dec. 3; Hopper, John (Box 3)
  - to Peter Lesley, 1850 Dec. 9; Clarke, James Freeman, 1810-1888 (Box 3)
  - to J. Peter Lesley, 1850 Dec. 10; Rogers, Henry D., (Henry Darwin), 1806-1866 (Box 3)
  - to Mrs. Lesley, 1850 Dec. 29; Loring, Louisa (Box 3)
  - to Mrs. Susan Lesley, 1850; Child, Lydia Maria, 1802-1880 (Box 3)
  - to Susan I. Lesley, 1851 Jan. 2; Head, Mary (Box 3)
  - to J. Peter Lesley, 1851 Jan. 3; Rogers, Henry D., (Henry Darwin), 1806-1866 (Box 3)
  - to J. Peter Lesley, 1851 Jan. 22; Rogers, William B. (Box 3)
  - Emma Rogers to Mrs. Susan I. Leslie [sic], 1851 Jan. 23 (Box 3)
  - Henry Harbaugh to Peter Lesley, 1851 Jan. 24 (Box 3)
  - to J. Peter Lesley, 1851 Jan. 24; Trumbull, David (Box 3)
  - to J. P. Lesley, 1851 Jan. 26; Rogers, William B. (Box 3)
  - to J. Peter Lesley, 1851 Jan. 27; Rogers, Henry D., (Henry Darwin), 1806-1866 (Box 3)
  - Edwards A. Parke to J. P. Lesley, 1851 Feb. 3 (Box 3)
  - to J. P. Lesley, 1851 Feb. 14; Trumbull, David (Box 3)
  - to J. Peter Lesley and Mrs. Susan Lesley, 1851 Feb. 17; Bost, Marie (Box 3)
  - to J. Peter Lesley, 1851 Feb. 22; Trumbull, David (Box 3)
  - to J. Peter Lesley, 1851 Mar. 5; Rogers, Henry D., (Henry Darwin), 1806-1866 (Box 3)
  - Francis Jackson to J. P. Lesley, 1851 Mar. 29 (Box 3)
  - Octavius Frothingham to Peter Lesley?, 1851 1851? Mar. (Box 3)
  - to J. Peter Lesley, 1851 Apr. 3; Rogers, Henry D., (Henry Darwin), 1806-1866 (Box 3)
  - to J. Peter Lesley, 1851 Apr. 9; Bost, Marie (Box 3)
  - Francis Jackson to J. P. Lesley, 1851 Apr. 18 (Box 3)
  - to J. P. Lesley, 1851 Apr. 22; Loring, Ellis Gray (Box 3)
  - to J. Peter Lesley, 1851 Apr. 29; Higginson, Thomas Wentworth, 1823-1911 (Box 3)
  - to J. P. Lesley, 1851 May 13; Haldeman, Samuel Stehman, 1812-1880 (Box 3)
  - to J. Peter Lesley, 1851 May 14; Jackson, R. M. S. (Box 3)
  - to J. Peter Lesley, 1851 May 15; Rogers, Henry D., (Henry Darwin), 1806-1866 (Box 3)
  - to J. Peter Lesley, 1851 May 17; Rogers, Henry D., (Henry Darwin), 1806-1866 (Box 3)
  - to J. P. Lesley, 1851 May 30; Haldeman, Samuel Stehman, 1812-1880 (Box 3)
  - to J. P. Lesley, 1851 May; Rogers, Henry D., (Henry Darwin), 1806-1866 (Box 3)
  - to J. P. Lesley, 1851 June 7; Thayer, W. S. (Box 3)
  - to Mr. and Mrs. J. Peter Lesley, 1851 June 22; Bost, Marie (Box 3)
  - to J. Peter Lesley, 1851 June 27; Rogers, Henry D., (Henry Darwin), 1806-1866 (Box 3)
  - to Comte Gorousky, 1851 June 28; Desor, Edouard (Box 3)
  - to J. P. Lesley, 1851 July 20; Desor, Edouard (Box 3)
  - to J. Peter Lesley, 1851 July 20; Rogers, Henry D., (Henry Darwin), 1806-1866 (Box 3)
  - to Henry D. Rogers, 1851 July 25; Lesley, J. P., (J. Peter), 1819-1903 (Box 3)
  - to Mr. and Mrs. J. Peter Lesley, 1851 July 28; Bost, Marie (Box 3)
  - to J. Peter Lesley, 1851 July 29; Rogers, Henry D., (Henry Darwin), 1806-1866 (Box 3)
  - to J. Peter Lesley, 1851 Aug. 2; Rogers, William B. (Box 3)
  - to Mrs. Lesley, 1851 Aug. 5; Child, Lydia Maria, 1802-1880 (Box 3)
  - to J. P. Lesley, 1851 Aug. 9; Rogers, Henry D., (Henry Darwin), 1806-1866 (Box 3)
  - to Mr. and Mrs. J. Peter Lesley, 1851 Sept. 1; Bost, Marie (Box 3)
  - to Mrs. Susan Lesley, 1851 Oct. 24; Bost, Marie (Box 3)
  - to Mrs. Susan Lesley, 1851 Oct. 24; Bost, Marie (Box 3)
  - to J. Peter Lesley, 1851 Oct. 28; Porter, John W. (Box 3)
  - to H. D. Rogers, 1851 Nov. 3; Lesley, J. P., (J. Peter), 1819-1903 (Box 3)
  - to J. P. Lesley, 1851 Nov. 4; Rogers, Henry D., (Henry Darwin), 1806-1866 (Box 3)
  - to J. PL Lesley, 1851 Nov. 5; Rogers, Henry D., (Henry Darwin), 1806-1866 (Box 3)
  - to J. Peter Lesley, 1851 Nov. 21; Lesquereux, Leo, 1806-1889 (Box 3)
  - to H. D. Rogers, 1851 Dec. 3; Lesley, J. P., (J. Peter), 1819-1903 (Box 3)
  - to H.D. Rogers, 1851 Dec. 11; Lesley, J. P., (J. Peter), 1819-1903 (Box 3)
  - to J. Peter Lesley, 1851 Dec. 26; Rogers, Henry D., (Henry Darwin), 1806-1866 (Box 3)
  - to Susie Mrs. Susan I. Lesley, ca. 1851; Hale, Edward Everett, 1822-1909 (Box 3)
  - to J. Peter Lesley, 1851 Wed. night; Rogers, Henry D., (Henry Darwin), 1806-1866 (Box 3)
  - to Peter Lesley, 1852 Jan. 9; Lesquereux, Leo, 1806-1889 (Box 4)
  - to E. Horsford, 1852 Jan. 14; Desor, Edouard (Box 4)
  - to J. P. Lesley, 1852 Feb. 16; Mann, Horace, 1796-1859 (Box 4)
  - Elizabeth Lesley to Peter Lesley, 1852 Feb. 2 (Box 4)
  - to Peter Lesley, 1852 Feb. 11; Clarke, James Freeman, 1810-1888 (Box 4)
  - to J. Peter Lesley, 1852 Feb. 22; Rogers, William B. (Box 4)
  - to J. P. Lesley, 1852 Feb. 25; Rogers, Henry D., (Henry Darwin), 1806-1866 (Box 4)
  - to J. Peter Lesley, 1852 March 1; Desor, Edouard (Box 4)
  - to Peter Lesley, 1852 March 12; Whelpley, J. D. (Box 4)
  - to Peter Lesley, 1852 March 17; Whelpley, J. D. (Box 4)
  - to H. D. Rogers, 1852 March25; Lesley, J. P., (J. Peter), 1819-1903 (Box 4)
  - to J. P. Lesley, 1852 March 26; Rogers, Henry D., (Henry Darwin), 1806-1866 (Box 4)
  - to J. Peter Lesley, 1852 March 27; Whelpley, J. D. (Box 4)
  - to H. D. Rogers, 1852 March 28; Lesley, J. P., (J. Peter), 1819-1903 (Box 4)
  - to Mrs. Busay Lesley, 1852 March 29; Child, Lydia Maria, 1802-1880 (Box 4)
  - to J. P. Lesley, 1852 March 30; Rogers, Henry D., (Henry Darwin), 1806-1866 (Box 4)
  - to J. Peter Lesley, 1852 April 12; Desor, Edouard (Box 4)
  - to J. Peter Lesley, 1852 May 1; Miller, Edward (Box 4)
  - to J. Peter Lesley, 1852 May 3; Washburn, Emory (Box 4)
  - to J. Peter Lesley, 1852 May 7; Miller, Edward (Box 4)
  - to J. Peter Lesley, 1852 May 8; Washburn, Emory (Box 4)
  - to J. Peter Lesley, 1852 May 14; Washburn, Emory (Box 4)
  - to J. Peter Lesley, 1852 May 16; Desor, Edouard (Box 4)
  - to J. Peter Lesley, 1852 May 28; Trumbull, David (Box 4)
  - Rudolph Barrigue to J. P. Lesley, 1852 June 14 (Box 4)
  - William Sydney Thayer to J. Peter Lesley, 1852 June 17 (Box 4)
  - to J. Peter Lesley, 1852 June 21; Lesquereux, Leo, 1806-1889 (Box 4)
  - to J. Peter Lesley, 1852 June 29; Watson, B. M. (Box 4)
  - to J. Peter Lesley, 1852 July 4; Desor, Edouard (Box 4)
  - to Peter Leslesy, 1852 July 25; Lesquereux, Leo, 1806-1889 (Box 4)
  - to J. Peter Lesley, 1852 August 14; Lesquereux, Leo, 1806-1889 (Box 4)
  - Lizzia ware to Mrs. Susan Lesley, 1852 August 22 (Box 4)
  - to J. Peter Lesley, 1852 August 28; Lesquereux, Leo, 1806-1889 (Box 4)
  - to J. Peter Lesley, 1852 September 28; Lesquereux, Leo, 1806-1889 (Box 4)
  - to J. Peter Lesley, 1852 Oct. 1; Barnes, Oliver W. (Box 4)
  - Carrie Morgan to Mrs. Susan Lesley, 1852 Oct. 21 (Box 4)
  - to J. Peter Lesley, 1852 Oct. 24; Desor, Edouard (Box 4)
  - to Mrs. Susan Lesley, 1852 Oct. 27; Bost, Marie (Box 4)
  - to J. Peter Lesley, 1852 Nov. 7; Lesquereux, Leo, 1806-1889 (Box 4)
  - to J. Peter Lesley, 1852 Nov. 21; Desor, Edouard (Box 4)
  - Misses Osgood to Mrs. Lesley, 1852 Nov. 30 (Box 4)
  - to J. Peter Lesley, 1852 Nov. 30; Quincy, Edmund (Box 4)
  - to Mrs. J. P. Susan Lesley, 1852 Dec. 14; Ware, Lizzie (Box 4)
  - to J. Peter Lesley, 1852 Dec. 18; Lesquereux, Leo, 1806-1889 (Box 4)
  - to J. Peter Lesley, 1852 Dec. 22; Higginson, Thomas Wentworth, 1823-1911 (Box 4)
  - to J. Peter Lesley, 1852 Dec. 28; Quincy, Edmund (Box 4)
  - to J. Peter Lesley, 1852 Wed. Morning; Desor, Edouard (Box 4)
  - to Peter Lesley, 1853 Jan. 5; Frothingham, Octavius Brooks (Box 4)
  - to Mrs. Susan Lesley, 1853 Jan. 5; Lyman, Joseph (Box 4)
  - to Mrs. Susan Lesley, 1853 Feb. 5; Guyot, A., (Arnold), 1807-1884 (Box 4)
  - to Mrs. Susan Leslsy, 1853 Feb. 13; Ware, Lizzie (Box 4)
  - to J. Peter Lesley, 1853 Feb. 28; Delano, Warren (Box 4)
  - Charles Summer to J. P. Lesley, 1853 March 6 (Box 4)
  - to Mrs. Susan Lesley, 1853 March 7; Bost, Marie (Box 4)
  - to Peter Lesley, 1853 March 12; Whelpley, Mrs. A. M. (Box 4)
  - to J. Peter Lesley, 1853 March 15; Wattson, L. T. (Box 4)
  - to J. Peter Lesley, 1853 March 17; Silliman, Benjamin, Jr. (Box 4)
  - to J. Peter Lesley, 1853 April 8; Bost, Timothy (Box 4)
  - to J. Peter Lesley, 1853 April 16; Lesquereux, Leo, 1806-1889 (Box 4)
  - to J. P. Lesley, 1853 April 18; Thayer, W. S. (Box 4)
  - George Stone. Receipt to W. W. Long for payment for a table once owned by Benjamin Franklin..., 1853 May 10 (Box 4)
  - to J. Peter Lesley, 1853 May 10; Tracy, Samuel F. (Box 4)
  - to C. Sherman, 1853 May 11; Lesley, J. P., (J. Peter), 1819-1903 (Box 4)
  - to J. Peter Lesley, 1853 May 18; Lesquereux, Leo, 1806-1889 (Box 4)
  - to J. Peter Lesley, 1853 May 31; Desor, Edouard (Box 4)
  - to J. Peter Lesley, 1853 June 28; Academy of Natural Sciences of Philadelphia. (Box 4)
  - Carrie Morgan to Mrs. Susie Lesley, 1853 June 29 (Box 4)
  - to Mrs. Susan Lesley, 1853 July 2; Lyman, Joseph (Box 4)
  - T. V. Moore to J. Peter Lesley, 1853 July 2 (Box 4)
  - to J. Peter Lesley, 1853 July 7; Wilkeson, William (Box 4)
  - to William Wilkeson., 1853 July 12; Lesley, J. P., (J. Peter), 1819-1903 (Box 4)
  - T. V. Moore to J. Peter Lesley, 1853 July 14 (Box 4)
  - to Mrs. Susan Lesley, 1853 July 24; Swan, Martha L. (Box 4)
  - to Mrs. Susan Lesley, 1853 August 1; Child, Lydia Maria, 1802-1880 (Box 4)
  - to J. Peter Lesley, 1853 Aug. 1; Pennsylvania Railroad. (Box 4)
  - to Mrs. Susan Lesley, 1853 August 19; Swan, Martha L. (Box 4)
  - C. M. Furness to "My dear friend" Mrs. Susan I. Lesley, 1853 August 28 (Box 4)
  - to Mr. and Mrs. J. Peter Lesley, 1853 August 31; Bost, Marie (Box 4)
  - to J. Peter Lesley, 1853 Aug. 31; Miller, Edward (Box 4)
  - Carrie Morgan to Mrs. Susan Lesley, 1853 Sept. 5 (Box 4)
  - to J. Peter Lesley, 1853 Sept. 9; Lesquereux, Leo, 1806-1889 (Box 4)
  - M. W. F. to Mrs. Susie I. Lesley, 1853 Sept. 29 (Box 4)
  - to J. Peter Lesley, 1853 Oct. 12; Gatiss, Henry (Box 4)
  - to J. Peter Lesley, 1853 Oct. 20; Gatiss, Henry (Box 4)
  - to Mrs. Susan Lesley, 1853 Oct. 25; Ware, Lizzie (Box 4)
  - to J. Peter Lesley, 1853 Oct. 26; Tracy, Samuel F. (Box 4)
  - Sarah H. Palmer to Mrs. Lesley, 1853 Oct. 31 (Box 4)
  - to J. Peter Lesley, 1853 Nov. 9; From Joseph P. Moore. (Box 4)
  - to J. Peter Lesley, 1853 Nov. 17; Gatiss, Henry (Box 4)
  - to J. Peter Lesley, 1853 Nov. 18; Gatiss, Henry (Box 4)
  - to J. Peter Lesley, 1853 Nov. 22; Gatiss, Henry (Box 4)
  - J. H. Morison to J. Peter Lesley, 1853 Dec. 7 (Box 4)
  - to J. Peter Lesley, 1853 Dec. 7; Tracy, Samuel F. (Box 4)
  - to Mrs. Susan Lesley, 1853 Dec. 9; Child, Lydia Maria, 1802-1880 (Box 4)
  - to Mr. and Mrs. J. Peter Lesley, 1853 Dec. 19; Bost, Marie (Box 4)
  - to Mrs. Susan Lesley, 1853 Dec. 29; Hopper, Rosa (Box 4)
  - Sarah H. Palmer to Mrs. Susan Lesley, 1853 Dec. (Box 4)
  - to J. Peter Lesley, [1853]; Miller, Edward (Box 4)